  <v lbl="Brief:Error">Oops, there's no briefing for this mission. Examine MISSION.INI and RA2.STR for examples of how to do this.</v>
  <v lbl="BRIEF:ALL01MD">Yuri Side has escaped away through Chrono transmission ! When we had time to react, he had mobilized a large group of troops to destroy the area on a large scale, through which Yuri Side seemed to be challenging us. Commander, be alert to any possible attacks at any time. It is not a good idea to confront him directly. Instead, we’d better keep our power to avoid more damage. 
Objective 1：send Tanya to the base in North to contact with it again. 
Objective 2：destroy the Psychic Dominator.
Objective 3：Tanya can’t die.</v>
  <v lbl="BRIEF:ALL02MD">According to the analysis of our information organization, the Chronosphere used by Yuri Side when he escaped is in the Hope Cape. It seems that Yuri Side has already occupied our most important Chronosphere base, which was once our fort against the Soviet Union. Therefore, if Yuri Side keeps occupying the base, it will threaten us greatly. At the same time, we must prevent Yuri Side from having enough time to thoroughly get Chrono technology or it will lead to a new catastrophe!

Objective 1：destroy the Psychic Beacon and rescue our coastal base.
Objective 2：occupy the war room so as to copy and destroy all our our files. 
Objective 3：destroy the Chronosphere before it is activated by Yuri Side again. </v>
  <v lbl="BRIEF:ALL03MD">when we were busy destroying the Chronosphere in the Hope Cape, Yuri Side had already focused on emphatically attacking Washington. Therefore, we hopelessly got into Yuri Side’s trap and Washington was in his control. Meanwhile, he deployed a Psychic Dominator here to consolidate his mental control over Washington. However, we just received an emergency call, saying that the president seems to have failed to get away from Washington because of time limit and is still trapped in the White House, so Commander, do not act slowly or the president will become flesh. 

Objective 1：destroy the Psychic Beacon before it is deployed again.
Objective 2：destroy the Psychic Dominator and remove the threat of super weapons 
Objective 3：wipe out all of Yuri’s forces</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:All04md">In recent battles, we were always passively disadvantaged and now, we have been driven up to wall. There is no doubt that Yuri Side’s running away this time makes him wiser, but fortunately we still have Dr. Einstein’s trump card---Time Machine. Therefore, if we can go back to the past, we would still have the chance to kill Yuri before he implements all of his conspiracies. Commander, this is our last chance, so be sure that the time machine will not be destroyed by him by all means. 

Objective 1：defend the time machine until it is activated.</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:ALL0Xmd">e went back to the past by the time machine, but Yuri Side had asked his troops to head for the Hope Cape, so if we can prevent him from getting our Chrono technology, the war will probably change. Therefore, Commander! Take up your arms and fight for a new history. 
 
Objective 1：contact with the base again.
Objective 2：destroy Yuri Side’s communication base. </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:All05md">Perhaps we are still one step slower as Yuri Side has already got some research achievements on chrono technology. For lack of enough technical support, he focused his attention on Einstein Chrono Scientific Research Base in Black Forest, Germany in the hope of capturing our scientists through mental control. According to our latest military intelligence, the Soviet Union also plans to take the advantage to make a profit this time, so we will be faced with two powerful opponents. Therefore, Commander, whatever happens, you need to defend the lab well!

Objective 1：destroy Yuri Side’s Psychic Dominator at full speed to stop his deployment.
Objective 2：destroy Soviet bases and troops. 
Objective 3：destroy Yuri Side’s front-line base.
Note: be sure to keep either the Chronosphere or Einstein Laboratory</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:All06md">we finally traced to the place where Yuri Side’s Chrono device gives out energy. It is located on an uncharted island in the Pacific ocean. Some of our well-organized troops are going to be sent to help you through Chrono transmission. Commander, you must be  extremely careful on the strange island! 

 
Objective 1：land on the island and build a Chronosphere base. 
Objective 2：destroy or occupy Yuri Side’s Chrono experimental device. 
Objective 3：destroy Yuri Side’s rocket before it is launched ! </v>
  <v lbl="BRIEF:ALL07MD">In remains of the rocket, we found the black box recording Yuri Side’s fight plan--it aimed to fly to the moon, so we believe that Yuri Side is probably hiding in his base there. In order to clearly know Yuri Side’s real conspiracy, we sent a group of task force to investigate there, which, however, lost touch with the headquarters. Commander, conquer the moon and kill the devil Yuri Side!

Objective 1：defend the rocket landing platform to wait for the reinforcements.
Objective 2：occupy Yuri Side’s command center to get his secret file. 
Objective 3：destroy all of Yuri Side’s forces</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov01md">it is strange that Yuri Side is still alive! Although we don’t know how much military power Yuri Side possesses now, according to the description of the urgent telegram from the Kremlin, some of Yuri Side’s forces appeared in Moscow, having gained some ground at full speed and cutting off the communication between the headquarters and Moscow forces. General, I don’t care whether Yuri Side threatens us or not now, you must get rid of the rubbish in Moscow as soon as possible, be quick!

Objective 1：occupy the communication center and connect with the base again. 
Objective 2：destroy all of Yuri Side’s forces. </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov02md">It was really terrible!---when we were busy dealing with Yuri Side’s surprise attack, the rest of some well-organized Allied forces had begun to fight against our regime, whose troops had already arrived in the sea area of Vladivostok. General, smash their foolish and babyish plan!
 
Objective 1：build a base.
Objective 2：destroy all Allied forces. </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov03md">General, because of our carelessness, Allied forces have taken some land back. According to the latest information analysis, American president has already returned the White House. General, you don’t wish to see another Capitalist regime that is against our Soviet in the world, do you? The position of the Communist Party is unshakable, so you need to capture American president and make Allied Nations surrender to us again!

Objective 1：build a military reserve base.
Objective 2：destroy guard troops around the White House and capture American president.  
Clue：you can get rewards after destroying landmark buildings. </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov04md">When we fought against Allied Nations, Yuri Side took the advantage to build a test base for Psychic Dominator. What does this mean if he is successful? I believe everyone knows the answer. General, you must destroy the Psychic Dominator as soon as possible so as to stifle his conspiracies in the cradle!

Objective 1：remove the threat from the Psychic Beacon and wait for the reinforcements. 
Objective 2：occupy the airport and get support from Allied forces.
Objective 3：destroy the Psychic Dominator at all costs </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov0xmd">Yuri Side’s forces are developing at a surprising speed. Therefore, after the prime minister and American president consulted with each other, they decided to smash his central area and capture him. The movement this time is adventurous, so General, you must be alert to emergencies at any time!

Objective 1：destroy Yuri Side’s Psychic Amplifier before he controls our forces.
Objective 2：destroy Yuri Side’s fort and capture him.  </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov05md">Emergency! When we were about to announce the official signature of world peace agreement, our satellites, workers of space stations found a large number of unknown objects were approaching the earth rapidly and some of them were near the moon. As is reported, they are troops from Antare---a T80 star cloud. It seems that we are going to occupy the moon at first and then command and control the earth to make it their colony! Ok, General, we have to fight again!
 
 
Objective 1：defend the experiment center until the new weapons are worked out. 
Objective 2：lock and destroy extra-terrestrial communication base on the moon. 
Objective 3：go back to the earth quickly</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov06md">General, Antare attacked us with irresistible force and we tried our best to destroy their forward-deployed forces arriving at the moon, but gave them enough time to get to the earth. The frontline of Moscow has fallen, so if Moscow is occupied, it will be a great disaster although the existing Star Battleships have been sent to each strategic center on the earth! A good news is that Allied Nations and some of troops that have surrendered to Yuri Side decided to join us and you are allowed to apply their technology. We don’t know the result of the war, so we should gather our strength to drive the bugs from Antare out of Moscow!
 
 
Objective 1：provide assistance to the Kremlin and help the prime minister to evacuate. 
Objective 2：coordinate Psychic Beacon to withstand Antare’s attacks. 
Objective 3：destroy the rest of Antare’s forces</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov07md">We detected that there was unknown action in Yuri Side’s nest in Romania. Then it was proved that the Allied forces and Soviet army defending there had lost contact with the headquarters and they were working on some regular scientific research activities. The premier worried it may be a conspiracy. The action this time is rather secret, so you must build the base at your fastest speed and bring the data away from the fort. 

Objective 1：destroy the Psychic Beacon and emancipate local Allied and Soviet forces 
Objective 2：send spies to the fort secretly to bring the data away. </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN01">The premier Yuri Side is trapped in Pacific Prison now. General, although it is defended closely here, our arms are well prepared and we have discovered a landing place on the east coast so as to save the premier as soon as possible and we will rise again!

Objective 1：enter into the psychic chamber to rescue premier Yuri.
Objective 2：look for and rescue the Mobile Construction Vehicle.
Objective 3：restore and activate the Psychic Beacon to capture American forces. 
Objective 4：Bring the premier into a helicopter safely and then leave. </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN02">We have successfully rescued the Premier and recollected some troops. However, because of limited materials, we need to have a military base. We aim at Yuri Island and plan to send an elite force to act. However, attention please, being unsatisfied with dictatorship of Allied Nations at present, the Soviet Union has already led off an attack to the island. Therefore, we need to make good use of the contradiction between them and don’t make Premier Yuri disappointed!

Objective 1：occupy Allied Battle Lab and control the rocket socket.
Objective 2：destroy the rest of American forces who are unwilling to surrender and occupy the island</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN03">We have already occupied Yuri Island, repaired lunar landing equipment and prepared for landing on the moon to implement the plan of controlling the air. General, it seems that there are many troops and important military secrets, so you must find out their weapon designs!

Objective 1：destroy Soviet control center to make it out of control 
Objective 2：occupy the control center to get the control over the Soviet base
Objective 3：destroy the signal transmission tower before the arrival of American reinforcements </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN04">We have taken a place on the moon but Soviet Red Army still threatens us greatly, so Premier Yuri plans to deploy a Psychic Beacon in Moscow to control the heartland of the Soviet Union, which is equal to controlling the whole Soviet Red Army. Of course, Moscow is guarded closely and taking action hastily will only make us lose more troops. Therefore, we sent a task force to give the Soviet Union an unprepared attack. At this time, when they have time to react, they are already controlled by our Psychic Beacon.


Objective 1：occupy NATECH to build a Psychic Beacon. 
Objective 2：activate the Psychic Beacon and capture the surrounding Soviet forces. 
Objective 3：destroy all of Soviet defense forces in Moscow and capture Romanov. </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN05">Premier of the Soviet Union surrendered and the next goal is American president. According to the present situation, America possesses the most powerful military forces among Allied Nations and has prism technology that has great threat. General, we must control America at the fastest speed and only in this way, can we achieve our ultimate purpose.

Objective 1：send will trucks to Soviet base to get the control over it.  
Objective 2：occupy Allied Battle Lab and get prism technology. 
Objective 3：occupy the White House and capture American president. </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN0X">Little time is left. Because of the excessive release of Soviet power, Premier Yuri is trapped in Jurassic Period. According to the latest information, after the Soviet Union won, American forces have built another time machine secretly, as if hoping to go back to the past to change the result. Therefore, we gathered some troops in the hope of occupying the time machine and rescuing premier Yuri. 

Objective 1：destroy coastal defence installations and American fleets. 
Objective 2：occupy the time machine.
Objective 3：kill the tyrannosaurus and make premier Yuri enter into our time machine.
Note: it is impossible for the Soviet to sit watching, so we need to look out for their sudden attacks. </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN06">Our psychic technology team has improved some performance of the Psychic Dominator and is planning to test it in Antarctica, and by the way occupy a Chronosphere abandoned by Allied Nations so as to research technology on Chrono travels. General, be careful as Allied Nations may find us at any time, so you must act quickly!

Objective 1：occupy the Chronosphere and wait for reinforcements.
Objective 2：destroy Weather Control Device and build a Psychic Dominator.
Objective 3：destroy the rest of Soviet and Allied forces.
Note：be sure that the Chronosphere is not destroyed </v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN07">American troops are now at the dead end, so they take out their last trump card----time machine to bet. How can we give these Yankees a chance to be arrogant again? General, just give America a bitter attack and I believe this war will be the final for American troops, so please complete the great chapter.

Objective 1：send infantries to occupy the communication center.  
Objective 2：lock and destroy the time machine.
Objective 3：look for and occupy the secret lab to get psychic technology.
Objective 4：build a Psychic Beacon and wait for the deployment.</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN08">Allied Nations broke up！What an inspiring news it is! But wait a moment, the former general Carville of Allied Nations and General Vladimir of the Soviet Union gathered the rest of their troops and built a naval base in Pearl Harbor. To some extent, they are the last leaders, so General, capture them and give them a summary execution!

Objective 1：clean up the troops stationing on the island, land on it and build a base there.  
Objective 2：land on Pearl Harbor to find out General Carville and General Vladimir  
Objective 3：take the generals of Allied Nations and the Soviet Union to the Soviet base to wait for their same ending as the Soviet base. </v>
<!--LoadMsg section-->
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All01md">Purple Light - location：Pacific Military Prison</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All02md">Space Crisis - location：Hope Cape in Alaska </v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All03md">Freedom and Compliance - location：Washington</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All04md">Gamble - location：the Sahara Desert（top secret location）</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:ALL0XMD">military action：Disordered Spacetime - location：Hope Cape in Alaska</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All05md">military action：Dark twilight - location: Black Forest in Germany</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All06md">military action：Dimensional Rift - location：an uncharted island on the Pacific ocean</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All07md">military action：Project Blue Book - location：Moon</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:ALL08MD">military action：__ - location：__</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov01md">military action：Revival -  location：Moscow</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov02md">military action：Agitation - location：Vladivostok</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov03md">military action：Rulers’ Action - location：Washington DC, America</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov04md">military action：Raids in North Africa - location：Morocco</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:SOV0XMD">military action：The Last Game -  location：Romania</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov06md">military action：Beleaguered - location：Moscow</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov05md">military action：In-depth Intercept - location：Moon</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov07md">military action：Hidden Stroke - location: Romania</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:SOV08MD">military action：__ - location：__</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN01">military action：Comeback- location: Pacific Military Prison</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN02">military action：Abyssal Raids - location：Easter Island, the Pacific Ocean</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN03">military action：Lunar Prospector - location：Moon </v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN04">military action: Twilight in Moscow - location：Moscow</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN05">military action: Washington Riot  location：Washington</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN06">military action：Polar Demon  location：Antarctic Peak </v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN07">military action：Escaping or Obeying location：San Francisco, California</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN08">military action：Execution on the Spot - location：Pearl Harbor, Pacific Ocean </v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN0X">secret military action：Spacetime Disorder  location：San Francisco, California</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:RES01">Biohazard: Dawn</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TEST01">task debugging：Allied Nations</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TEST02">task debugging：the Soviet Union</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TEST03">task debugging：Yuri Side</v>
<!--LoadBrief section-->
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All01md">Objective 1：send Tanya to the base in North to contact with it again. 
Objective 2：destroy the Psychic Dominator.
Objective 3：Tanya can’t die</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All02md">Objective 1：destroy the Psychic Beacon and rescue our coastal base.  
Objective 2：occupy the war room so as to copy and destroy all our our files.  
Objective 3：destroy the Chronosphere before it is activated by Yuri Side again.</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All03md">Objective 1：destroy the Psychic Beacon before it is deployed again. 
Objective 2：destroy the Psychic Dominator and remove the threat of super weapons
Objective 3：wipe out all of Yuri’s forces</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All04md">Objective 1：defend the time machine until it is activated </v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All0xmd">Objective 1：contact with the base again.
Objective 2：destroy Yuri Side’s communication base.</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All05md">Objective 1：destroy Yuri Side’s Psychic Dominator at full speed to stop his deployment.
Objective 2：destroy Soviet bases and troops.
Objective 3：destroy Yuri Side’s front-line base.
Note: be sure to keep either the Chronosphere or Einstein Laboratory</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All06md">Objective 1：land on the island and build a Chronosphere base.
Objective 2：destroy or occupy Yuri Side’s Chrono experimental device. 
Objective 3：destroy Yuri Side’s rocket before it is launched ! </v>
  
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All07md">Objective 1：defend the rocket landing platform to wait for the reinforcements.
Objective 2：occupy Yuri Side’s command center to get his secret file. 
Objective 3：destroy all of Yuri Side’s forces</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov01md">Objective 1：occupy the communication center and connect with the base again. Objective 2：destroy all of Yuri Side’s forces</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov02md">Objective 1：build a base.
Objective 2：destroy all Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov03md">Objective 1：build a military reserve base.
Objective 2：destroy guard troops around the White House and capture American president.
Clue：you can get rewards after destroying landmark buildings. </v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov04md">Objective 1：remove the threat from the Psychic Beacon and wait for the reinforcements. 
Objective 2：occupy the airport and get support from Allied forces.
Objective 3：destroy the Psychic Dominator at all costs </v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov0xmd">Objective 1：destroy Yuri Side’s Psychic Amplifier before he controls our forces.
Objective 2：destroy Yuri Side’s fort and capture him.</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov05md">Objective 1：defend the experiment center until the new weapons are worked out. Objective 2：lock and destroy extra-terrestrial communication base on the moon. Objective 3：go back to the earth quickly</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov06md">Objective 1：provide assistance to the Kremlin and help the prime minister to evacuate.
Objective 2：coordinate Psychic Beacon to withstand Antare’s attacks. 
Objective 3：destroy the rest of Antare’s forces</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov07md">Objective 1：destroy the Psychic Beacon and emancipate local Allied and Soviet forces
Objective 2：send spies to the fort secretly to bring the data away. </v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN01">Objective 1：enter into the psychic chamber to rescue premier Yuri
Objective 2：look for and rescue the Mobile Construction Vehicle.
Objective 3：restore and activate the Psychic Beacon to capture American forces
Objective 4：bring the premier into a helicopter safely and then leave. </v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN02">Objective 1: occupy Allied Battle Lab and control the rocket socket.
Objective 2：destroy the rest of American forces who are unwilling to surrender and occupy the island</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN03">Objective 1：destroy Soviet control center to make its base out of control.  
Objective 2：occupy the control center to get the control over the Soviet base
Objective 3：destroy the signal transmission tower before the arrival of American reinforcements </v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN04">Objective 1：occupy NATECH to build a Psychic Beacon.
Objective 2：activate the Psychic Beacon and capture the surrounding Soviet forces.
Objective 3：destroy all of Soviet defense forces in Moscow and capture Romanov. </v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN05">Objective 1：send orders to Soviet base to get the control over it.  
Objective 2：occupy Allied Battle Lab and get prism technology. 
Objective 3：occupy the White House and capture American president. </v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN06">Objective 1:occupy the Chronosphere and wait for reinforcements.
Objective 2：destroy Weather Control Device and build a Psychic Dominator.
Objective 3：destroy the rest of Soviet and Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN07">Objective 1：send infantries to occupy the communication center.  
Objective 2：lock and destroy the time machine.
Objective 3：look for and occupy the secret lab to get psychic technology.
Objective 4：build a Psychic Beacon and wait for the deployment.</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN08">Objective 1：clean up the troops stationing on the island, land on it and build a base there.  
Objective 2：land on Pearl Harbor find out General Carville and General Vladimir
 Objective 3：take the generals of Allied Nations and the Soviet Union to the Soviet base to wait for their same ending as the Soviet base. </v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN0X">Objective 1：destroy coastal defence installations and American fleets.
Objective 2：occupy the time machine.
Objective 3：kill the tyrannosaurus and make premier Yuri enter into our time machine.
Note: it is impossible for the Soviet to sit watching, so we need to look out for their sudden attacks. </v>
  <v lbl="Mission:ExtremeHam">Extreme Ham</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Objective1">Objective 1 Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Objective2">Objective 2 Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Objective3">Objective 3 Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01a">Objective 1: Assign your infantry to enter the Psychic Isolation Chamber to save Premier Yuri, ATTENTION: DO NOT DESTROY THE CHAMBER.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01b">ATTENTION: Premier Yuri came out, keep him safe.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01c">MCV received, ready to build the base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01d">Reinforcements have arrived, waiting for your orders.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01e">Objective 4: Send Premier Yuri to the helicopter and get out from here.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01f">Satellite has reconnected.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01g">HINT: Repair the bridge so that our forces can go and pass.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01h">There's no ore or gems here, capture the OIL DERRICK to acquire resources.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01i">Objective 3: Capture and activate the Psychic Beacon.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01j">MCV is sighted! Go for it right now!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01k">Repair the abandoned Psychic Beacon.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02b">Objective 1: Capture the Allied Battle Lab, and control the Rocket Launch Pad.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02c">General, here's an open space, you can land here and build the base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02d">Elite naval forces have arrived, awaiting orders.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02e">ALERT: Allied Battle Lab is destroyed, we lost control of the rocket.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02f">ALERT: Launch Pad structure lost. Mission Failed.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02g">Objective 2: Destroy all enemy Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02h">Objective 1 Completed.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02i">WARNING: Soviet naval forces detected.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02_Hint1">Deploy your GIs near the entrance to your base for a better defense</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02_Hint2">The Premier successfully retreated. Mission Accomplished.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02_Hint3">Now is not the time for potty breaks, Commander</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02_Hint4">No time to sit, Commander</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02hAlt">WARNING: The stench of Red Team is in the air</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01a">Objective 1: Destroy all four Soviet DREADNOUGHTS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01b">Objective 2: Rendezvous with FORT BRADLEY</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01c">HINT: Order your GI's to enter CIVILIAN BUILDINGS to fortify them</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01d">HINT: Fuel barrels explode if destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01e">HINT: Your base is out of power, build more power plants</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01f">HINT: Construct a BARRACKS in order to produce ENGINEERS to repair the bridge</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01g">HINT: GI's must DEPLOY to enter or exit their sandbagged foxholes</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01h">Objective 3: Destroy the Soviet SUPPLY BASE</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01i">WARNING: Soviet PARATROOPERS are incoming</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02a">Head NORTH and make contact with American forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02b">Objective 1: Use ENGINEERS to re-capture our base to the NORTH WEST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02c">Objective 2: Destroy all hostile forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02d">HINT: Order an ENGINEER into any HOSTILE BUILDING to capture the building</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02e">HINT: Order TANYA to destroy the FLAK CANNONS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02f">HINT: TANYA can swim</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04a">Objective 1: Clear enemy shore defenses with your Destroyers, then land and establish a base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04b">Objective 2: Destroy the Soviet's Psychic Amplifier before it comes online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04c">Estimated time until Psychic Amplifier is online:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All09a">Objective 1: Capture or Eliminate Soviet Research Facility within the Pyramid Ruins</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All09b">Objective 2: Destroy the Soviet base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All09c">Objective 1 Accomplished</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All09d">Objective 2 Accomplished</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov01a">Objective 1: Destroy the Pentagon</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1b">HINT: Order an ENGINEER into the BRIDGE HUT to repair the bridge</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1c">HINT: Order your CONSCRIPTS to enter CIVILIAN BUILDINGS to fortify them</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1d">HINT: FLAK TRACKS can carry TROOPS into battle</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1e">HINT: Your base is OUT OF POWER, build Power Plants</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1f">HINT: Fuel barrels EXPLODE if destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1g">HINT: Capture the AIRPORT with an ENGINEER to allow your paratroopers to land in the area</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02a">Objective 1: Force a beach landing and build a base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02b">Objective 2: Destroy all enemy forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02c">Vladimir: Now is the time to strike</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02d">Vladimir: What are you waiting for General? Do something!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02e">Enemy Fleet detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02f">Vladimir has fled the battlefield!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02g">Your Mobile Construction Vehicle has landed. Double-click on it to create a Construction Yard</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03a">Objective 1: Capture the Allied BATTLE LAB with an ENGINEER</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03b">Technology gained - Build a PSYCHIC BEACON</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03bb">Technology gained - PSYCHIC BEACON placed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03c">Objective 2: Defend the PSYCHIC BEACON from Allied attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03d">Beacon Deployment in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03e">Allied troops are now under Soviet control</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03f">Objective 3: Defeat all remaining Allied troops</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04a">Time until Allied invasion begins:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04b">Hint: Build Flak Cannons to engage Allied aircraft</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04c">Allied Forces have landed!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04d">Objective 1: Establish a base to defend our motherland</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04e">Objective 2: Drive the Allied invaders back into the sea</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov05a">Objective 1: Energize the PARIS TOWER with 3 TESLA TROOPERS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov05b">Objective 2: Defend the PARIS TOWER from Allied attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov05c">Objective 3: Defeat all remaining Allied troops</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov05d">HINT: Cars + Bombs = CarBombs!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06b">Estimated time until Korean Fleet arrives:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07a">Objective 1: Defend your Battle Lab against waves of Allied attackers</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07b">General Carville has stationed a truck near one of our villages; He has been broadcasting capitalist propaganda in an attempt to turn our people against us</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07c">I think we should send a few dogs to sniff out enemy spies</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07d">The first wave of Allied troops have entered the Chronosphere</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07e">Another Allied force has entered the Chronosphere</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07f">The final Allied troops have entered the Chronosphere</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07g">You've captured a powerful new enemy vehicle! Try putting different infantry inside to enhance the vehicle's abilities</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07h">CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST: Our Battle Lab has been captured</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07i">CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST: Spies have infiltrated our Battle Lab</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07j">CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST: Our Battle Lab has been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov08a">Objective 1: Capture the White House so we can apprehend the traitor Vladimir</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov08b">Destroy monuments for cash bonuses from the Kremlin!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov09a">Objective 1: Use Mind-Control to capture the President</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov09b">Use America's own soldiers against them</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov09c">Enemy bases detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov09d">Order spies to enter power plants to sabotage base power</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov10a">Objective 1: Capture the BATTLE LAB with an ENGINEER</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov12a">Build naval forces and invade the Allied base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov12b">Move north and reclaim our captured Kirov airships</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov12c">Objective 1: Destroy the Allied CHRONOSPHERE</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12a">Objective 1: Clear the area so Chrono Reinforcements can arrive</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12b">Objective 2: Eliminate Romanov's Elite Black Guard around the Kremlin.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12c">Objective 2 Accomplished - Romanov has been captured</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12d">Objective 1 Accomplished - Chrono Reinforcements can now arrive</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12e">Alliance formed with Soviet Defectors</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12f">Soviet resource stockpile detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12g">Allied chrono reinforcements in transit, arriving soon</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01cc">Move your troops across the bridge</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02iAlt">Objective 2: Deploy your MCV into a Construction Yard</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01j">Secondary Objective Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01k">New Objective Received</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01l">HINT: Seals can SWIM and PLANT C4 like Tanya</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01m">HINT: Cars can be used to CARRY INFANTRY. To remove passengers, double-click on the car</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01n">HINT: Chrono Harvesters HARVEST ore and then automatically TELEPORT back to their refinery</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01o">HINT: Select the infantry TAB to view additional PRODUCTION OPTIONS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01p">HINT: Order your ENGINEER into one of the REPAIR HUTS in order to fix the bridge</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01q">--Battle Control Online--</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01r">Additional troops gained</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01s">HINT: To REMOVE your troops, DOUBLE-CLICK on the occupied building</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01t">HINT: DOUBLE-CLICK the GI's to switch them between DEPLOYED and MOBILE states</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01u">These GI's have deployed their heavy machine guns.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01v">Tanya has died - CRITICAL UNIT LOST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01w">The STATUE OF LIBERTY has been destroyed - CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01x">The STATUE OF LIBERTY is about to be destroyed - Hurry and destroy the Dreadnoughts!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01y">HINT: To REMOVE your troops, SELECT the occupied building, then click on it again.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02g">Keep TANYA alive!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02h">TANYA has been KILLED!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02i">so the ROCKETEERS can destroy the SENTRY GUNS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03a">Objective 1: Destroy the Psychic Beacon</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03b">You have salvaged Allied units abandoned after the Soviet invasion</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03c">HINT: Beware of SOVIET TROOPS garrisoned in CIVILIAN STRUCTURES</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03d">HINT: Be careful NOT to destroy the White House... we don't want to endanger the President</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03e">MISSION FAILED: Nice job commander. You've managed to crush the President under a huge slab of concrete...</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03f">HINT: Send an ENGINEER into a damaged CIVILIAN STRUCTURE to repair it</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03g">HINT: Try putting different INFANTRY in your new IFV to use its morphing ability</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03h">MISSION FAILED: President Dugan is but a flattened shell of a man</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03i">Straggler units from across the Potomac have gathered up near the Lincoln Memorial</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03j">A brave group of Allied survivors has scraped together a squad near the Smithsonian</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03k">HINT: Order an ENGINEER into an IFV to transform it into a Mobile Repair Vehicle</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04d">Reinforcements have just arrived from our Canadian base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04e">More reinforcements have just arrived from across Lake Michigan</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04f">HINT: Enemy SUB PATROLS are all over Lake Michigan. Land your transports quickly to avoid losses</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04g">Objective 2: Destroy the Psychic Amplifier before it comes online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04h">HINT: Send INFANTRY into the HOSPITAL to restore them to full health</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04i">HINT: These OIL DERRICKS, if captured, will yield a steady flow of cash</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04j">Clear the shore defenses with your Destroyers, then land and establish your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05a">Objective 1: Infiltrate the Soviet Battle Lab with a Spy</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05b">Objective 2: Eliminate the two Soviet Nuclear Missile Silos</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05c">HINT: SPIES can disguise themselves as ENEMY TROOPS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05d">HINT: To disguise a SPY, select him and left click on an ENEMY SOLDIER</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05e">Tesla Coil detected - CAUTION: EXTREME DANGER</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05f">Additional Spies have arrived</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05g">Allied patrol discovered</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05h">Secondary Objective Complete - NEW OBJECTIVE RECEIVED</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05i">Primary Objective Complete - MISSION SUCCESSFUL</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05j">Bovine rescued</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05k">Tanya has died - CRITICAL UNIT LOST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05l">The Battle Lab has been destroyed - CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05m">First Nuclear Missile Silo destroyed - one remaining</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05n">First Nuclear Missile Silo has been captured - one remaining</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05o">HINT: Send a SPY into a TESLA REACTOR to shut down all base defenses</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05p">Silo coordinates acquired successfully - Enlarging map size to compensate</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05q">--Battle Control Online--</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05r">Somewhere in Poland...</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05s">Signal Flare Detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07b">WARNING - SOVIET ATTACK IMMINENT</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08T">Time until Beacon affects Tanya:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10a1">HINT: When the MIRAGE TANK stops, it</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10a2">cloaks itself as a TREE and waits to ambush</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10a3">passing enemy forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10c">WARNING: Einstein's Laboratory is under attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10e">Objective 2: Destroy all Soviet invaders</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11d">Objective 1: Construct a Chronosphere</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12h">Tanya lost</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12i">Kremlin Infiltrated - PRIMARY OBJECTIVE COMPLETE</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02h">Build a NAVAL YARD so you can construct SUBMARINES</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03aa">HINT: Capture the OIL DERRICKS for extra resources</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06c">A small fleet of the new Soviet Dreadnought has arrived</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06d">A small fleet of the new Soviet Dreadnought has arrived.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07k">Allied Spy Sat maps were found in the Propaganda Truck wreckage... updating map.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov08c">Destroy monuments for bonuses from the Kremlin!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov08d">Objective 1: Capture the White House</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11a">Objective 1: Destroy the KREMLIN, where YURI is cowering</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11b">WARNING: Enemy air armada detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11c">WARNING: Yuri has detected our Nuclear Missile Silo - Defend it well</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11d">HINT: To stop Kirov Airships, build lots of Flak Cannons</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11e">Hey! You're not supposed to be here!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11f">11/21/98</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11g">Power-up Crate discovered!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11h">NOX ROX!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11i">Warning, Iron Curtain device detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11j">Warning, the Iron Curtain device has rendered some of Yuri's troops invulnerable</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11k">TSC&amp;ACC</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11l">WARNING: Enemy Armor Brigade detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11m">WARNING: Enemy Infantry Platoon detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11n">WARNING: Enemy Naval Fleet detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06a1">Objective 1: Reinforce and take command</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06a2">of Allied forces near the Pentagon</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06b1">Objective 2: Eliminate all Soviet forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06b2">occupying Washington, DC</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06c1">HINT: The SERVICE DEPOT can safely remove</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06c2">Soviet TERROR DRONES from infected vehicles</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06d1">Pentagon forces transferred to your command</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06d2">Objective 1 Accomplished</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07a1">Objective 1: Destroy all Soviet forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07a2">on or around the Hawaiian Islands</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07c1">HINT: The GAP GENERATOR will conceal your</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07c2">base from Soviet nuclear attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08a1">Objective 1: Capture or Destroy the</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08a2">Psychic Beacon before it affects your team</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08b1">Objective 2: Drive all Soviet forces out</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08b2">of St. Louis</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08c1">WARNING: Soviet Desolators have irradiated</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08c2">the ground at this location</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08d1">WARNING: The Psychic Beacon has affected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08d2">your team</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10b1">ALERT! Soviet Invasion Forces Detected. ALERT!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10d1">Objective 1: Defend Professor Einstein's</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10d2">Laboratory</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11a1">HINT: To make SQUID release a ship, you</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11a2">must force your DOLPHINS to fire on the</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11a3">AFFECTED SHIP</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11b1">HINT: The CHRONOSPHERE will teleport all</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11b2">VEHICLES within a small area across any distance</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11c1">WARNING: Soviet Nuclear Missiles are now</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11c2">being armed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11e1">Objective 2: Neutralize the Soviet Nuclear</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11e2">Missile Silos</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11T">Nuclear Strike in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06d1">Use them for long range shore bombardment.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov6a">Objective 1: Establish a base on the Hawaiian Islands</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06g">Objective 2: Destroy the Allied fleet</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07L">Enemy Forces Arriving In:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1H">Iwo Jima Victory Monument, Washington D.C.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov10d">MISSION CRITICAL STRUCTURE - Do not destroy!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov10b">HINT: Build a NUCLEAR MISSILE SILO</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov10c">Objective 2: Destroy the Weather Control Device</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08e">Bonus Discovered. Timer Extended.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL12y">Special Agent Tanya has arrived.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL12z">Final Objective: Tanya will infiltrate the Kremlin and Capture Romanov</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03m">HINT: Order GIs into nearby CIVILIAN BUILDINGS to fortify them.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:HINTGENERAL">HINT: Order CONSCRIPTS into nearby CIVILIAN BUILDINGS to fortify them.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04k">HINT: AIR UNITS are very effective for assaults on Soviet-occupied civilian structures</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04l">Objective 1: Establish a base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL11zz">Order a SPY into an enemy NUKE to reset the count down.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL12zz">Romanov must be captured. Don't destroy the Kremlin!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04m">Deploy your Mobile Construction Vehicle into a Construction Yard</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GetPower">Objective: Capture Power Plants to bring the Time Machine online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:KillRuss">Objective: Destroy all Soviet tanks</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Alcatraz">Objective: Swim Tanya to Alcatraz Island and destroy the Psychic Dominator</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Soviets">Objective: Clear the area of Soviet forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Carriers">Aircraft Carrier reinforcements have arrived</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Seals">SEAL reinforcements have arrived</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TimeText">Time Machine:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Swim">Hint: Tanya can swim to Alcatraz Island</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GrandC">Hint: Use the Grand Cannons to take out the Nuclear Reactor on Alcatraz</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GrandC2">Hint: Use the Grand Cannons to take out Soviet Dreadnoughts</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Tanya2">Hint: Tanya can plant C4 charges on tanks</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Soviet2">WARNING - Soviet armor battallion detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Attack">WARNING - The Time Machine is under attack!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Attack2">WARNING - Our Power Plants are under attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Attack3">WARNING - Do not attack Power Plants!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GattCann">WARNING - Gattling Cannon detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LoseTM">The Time Machine has been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LosePowr">There are not enough Power Plants left to charge the Time Machine</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Grinders">Objective: Destroy all Grinders in the city</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriBase">Objective: Destroy all enemy buildings</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LAX">Hint: Capture LAX to gain access to paratroopers</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Money">Hint: We may be able to salvage funds from Yuri's Grinders when they are destroyed.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Heroes">Hint: Action Heroes are excellent against infantry. Use them to eliminate Yuri Clones</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Lose">Your base has been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RescueMS">Secondary Objective: Liberate the MassiveSoft Campus from Yuri's goons</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:KillNuke">Objective: Destroy Yuri's Nuclear Silo</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RescueEinstein">Objective: Rescue Einstein from Yuri's secret base near the Great Pyramid</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyYuri04A">Objective: Destroy Yuri's main base in the East</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DerrickHint">Hint: Send engineers into the oil derricks in the East to increase cash flow</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:BoomerAttack">WARNING - Yuri is sending Boomer subs our way! Prepare for confrontation!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyCloning">Objective: Destroy Yuri's Cloning facility in the South</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyYuri05A">Objective: Destroy Yuri's remaining forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Fuego">Objective: Use engineers to bring the Soviet base back online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Radar">Objective: Build a Soviet Radar Dish</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:KillPD">Objective: Destroy the Psychic Dominator on Antarctica</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:KillYuri">Destroy all of Yuri's structures</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:FindRomanov">Objective: Locate Premier Romanov before Yuri's troops do</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RecoverRomanov">Objective: Rescue Romanov from Yuri's control</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyYuri04S">Objective: Destroy Yuri's base around the airport so Romanov can be safely evacuated</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TakeRomanov">Objective: Take Romanov to the airport where he can be transported away safely</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:BuildBase">Objective: Find a location to set up base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyLunarCommand">Objective: Locate and destroy Yuri's Lunar Command Center</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyYuri06S">Objective: Destroy all remaining Yuri buildings</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:NukeHint">HINT: Yuri also relies on Power Plants for his Nuclear Silo</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sniper">Sniper reinforcements arriving</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:PowerAtk">WARNING - Our Power Plants are under attack!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Virus">Hint: Snipers have a longer range than the Virus</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Virus2">Hint: The Virus has a longer range than Snipers</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Cloud">WARNING - Infantry will take damage if standing within a Virus cloud</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LowPower">Capture Power Plants to bring the Weather Control Device online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Needle">Hint: Garrison the Space Needle to survey the area</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriMove">WARNING - Yuri is attempting to engineer our Power Plants</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriTimer">Yuri Forces Arriving In:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ParlHint">Hint: Repair Parliament with an Engineer</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:StopYuri">Objective: Destroy all Yuri forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MixUnits">Hint: Combine Soviet infantry with our IFV's for more powerful units</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:PDHint">Hint: Spread our units out so that the Psychic Dominator won't be able to mind control large masses of our forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GMHint">Hint: Spread out our infantry so that Yuri will not be able to use the Genetic Mutator on large groups of units.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TmeTimer">Time Machine Recharged in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TranHint">Hint: Build Amphibious Transports</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RexyHelp">Rexy is trapped! Won't you help him?</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RexyFrnd">Rexy is now your friend to the end!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:WarnStct">WARNING - Critical structure. Do not destroy!!!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MoreTrps">More of our troops have arrived on the beach</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MoreEngn">Engineers have arrived near the Time Machine</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriPowr">Yuri is trying to capture the Power Plants!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YGotPowr">Yuri captured a Power Plant!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:HintPowr">Hint: Capture Power Plants with Engineers</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DomArmed">The Psychic Dominator is now armed!!!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:HintDom">Hint: Capturing Power Plants will stop the Psychic Dominator</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriHovr">Yuri Hover Transports approaching!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LostAll">All Soviet forces lost</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:NoTroops">No remaining Soviet forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LostStct">Critical Structure Lost</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LostUnit">Critical Unit Lost</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:WarnArmd">WARNING - The Psychic Dominator is Armed!!!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:WrnAmbsh">WARNING - Possible Ambush Ahead!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:WarnSnpe">WARNING - Sniper detected!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:SecrtLab">Secret Laboratory Acquired!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ScrtTech">Secret Technology Acquired!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All6Obj1">Objective 1: Defend Parliament from Assault.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All6Obj2">Objective 2: Destroy Yuri's Base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj1">Objective 1: Destroy the Allied Navy and Grand Cannons.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj2">Objective 2: Destroy Pill Boxes around Time Machine to capture it.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj3">Objective 3: Capture 4 Power Plants to Power Time Machine.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj4">Objective 4: Take Control of Soviet Base and use it to Destroy the Psychic Dominator.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj5">Objective: Defend the Time Machine until it can be reactivated.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj6">Find the Soviet Base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj7">Destroy the Psychic Dominator.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj1Comp">Objective 1 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj2Comp">Objective 2 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj3Comp">Objective 3 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj4Comp">Objective 4 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj5Comp">Objective 5 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj6Comp">Objective 6 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj7Comp">Objective 7 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj8Comp">Objective 8 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj9Comp">Objective 9 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov2Obj1">Objective 1: Destroy the outposts guarding the German border.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov2Obj2">Objective 2: Destroy Einstein's Lab and Chronosphere.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Mirage">WARNING - Mirage Tanks spotted!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MirageHint">Hint: Mirage tanks become visible if they move or fire.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:BattleFortress">WARNING - The Battle Fortress can crush tanks. Destroy them before they can close in.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:IndustrialHint">Hint: Build an Industrial Plant to speed up production.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:SpyPlaneHint">Hint: Use the Spy Plane to uncover shroud.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov3Obj1">Objective 1: Destroy the Psychic Beacon.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov3Obj2">Objective 2: Destroy the Psychic Dominator.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov3Obj3">Objective 3: Finish off Yuri's forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov5Obj1">Objective 1: Pick a landing zone and construct a base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov5Obj2">Objective 2: Locate and destroy Yuri's Submarine Pen.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov5Obj3">Objective 3: Finish off all remaining Yuri land forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MojoTip">Mojo 1</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Clones">HINT: Use attack dogs to deal with Yuri Clones and Initiates</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:AllGone">Our forces have been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GrabPowr">HINT: Capture Power Plants to bring the Weather Control Device back online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ReinforcementsAll04md">Reinforcements have arrived and await orders from your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RobotTanks">Hint: Robot Tanks are psychic immune</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:SniperDiscovered">Look, there was a sniper lost in the desert! He's happy to be a part of your team!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ImportDino">Thanks to ChronoSphere technology we were able import dinosaurs to help us defeat Yuri!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Mojo1All04md">You can feel the presence of Mojo One</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ReinforcementsAll05md">Reinforcements have arrived and await orders from your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TopSecret">You've discovered something no one has ever seen before!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:BuildUp">Build up your defenses quickly before Yuri's attack forces arrive!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Boomers">WARNING - Boomer Subs spotted off the Antarctic coast</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Lose1">We have lost our foothold in Antarctica</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Lose2">All of our forces have been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Lose3">We have lost the ability to build radar</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ReinforcementsSov04md">Reinforcements have arrived and await orders from your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:PolarBears">It looks like these bears were tired of the cold!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ReinforcementsSov06md">Reinforcements have arrived and await orders from your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:AllyBeacon">Hint: Capture or Destroy the Psychic Beacon in the Allied Base to release them from Yuri's control.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:SovBeacon">Hint: Neutralize the Psychic Beacon controlling the Soviet Base and they will rally to your side against Yuri.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07Obj01">Objective: Destroy Yuri's Fortress.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:HiKBOAEO">KBO AEO</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ComboWarn01">WARNING - Yuri has begun mixing the technologies at his disposal.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ComboWarn02">Make ready for these attacks.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GeneWarn">WARNING - Yuri's Genetic Mutator mutates normal soldiers, turning them into Brutes under Yuri's control.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C11Obj">Objective: Destroy all Soviet forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C11Nuke">Destroy the Soviets Nuclear Reactor.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C12Obj">Objective: Destroy all Yuri forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C12Spy">Hint: Use a Spy to shut down Yuri's power.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C13Def">Construct base defenses before enemy forces arrive.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C13Timer">Enemy forces arrive in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C13Warn">WARNING - Enemy troop movements detected.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C13Obj">Objective: Destroy all Yuri and Soviet forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C21Timer">Reinforcements arrive in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C21Grand">Destroy the Allied Grand Cannons.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C21Obj">Destroy all Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C22Gatt">Destroy Yuri's Gattling Cannon defenses.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C23Obj">Objective: Destroy all Yuri and Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C23Lab">Locate and capture Einstein's laboratory.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C23Nuke">Protect the Nuclear Reactors.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C31Obj">Objective: Destroy all Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C31Crate">Hint: Destroy American monuments for a cash reward.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C32Navy">Build Boomer Submarines to destroy the Soviet Navy.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C33Obj">Objective: Destroy all Allied and Soviet forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C33">Hint: Target civilians with the Genetic Mutator to turn them into Brutes.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Combo">HINT:Try using combinations of Allied and Soviet units.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Hsptl">HINT: Capture the Tech Hospital to regenerate infantry health.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Mshop">HINT: Capture the Tech Machine Shop to regenerate vehicle armor.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Rig">HINT: Capture Tech Oil Derricks to increase cash flow.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Air">HINT: Capture the Tech Airport for Airborne reinforcements.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ObjCompleteSov04md">Objective Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DominatorSelfDestruct">Psychic Dominator Self Destruct</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:PsychicTowers">WARNING - Psychic Towers can mind control enemy units that get too close to them!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj2a">Destroy the Pill Boxes surrounding the Time Machine.</v>
