  <v lbl="Brief:Error">Oops, there's no briefing for this mission. Examine MISSION.INI and RA2.STR for examples of how to do this.</v>
  <v lbl="BRIEF:ALL01MD">尤里通过超时空传送逃脱了！当我们反应过来时，尤里已经调动了一大批部队大规模毁灭这座区域，似乎尤里想借此向我们挑衅。指挥官，随时留意可能的袭击，与尤里正面对抗并不是很好的决断，我们应当保留实力，避免更大的损失。

任务目标一：派谭雅进入北方的基地，与基地重新取得联络。
任务目标二：摧毁心灵控制器。
任务目标三：谭雅不能殉职。</v>
  <v lbl="BRIEF:ALL02MD">根据我们情报机构的分析，尤里逃脱时使用的超时空传送仪位于希望角。看来尤里早已经占领了我们最为重要的超时空传送仪基地，那座基地曾经是我们对抗苏联的要塞，如果让尤里继续占据那座基地，将会对我们构成极大威胁。同时，我们不能让尤里有足够的时间去掌握超时空传送技术，这将导致一场新的灾难！
 
任务目标一：摧毁心灵信标，解救我方沿海基地。
任务目标二：占领作战室以备份并销毁所有我方资料。
任务目标三：在尤里再次启动超时空传送仪之前，将其摧毁。</v>
  <v lbl="BRIEF:ALL03MD">正当我们忙于摧毁希望角的超时空传送仪时，尤里早已将进攻重点置于华盛顿。我们很无奈地落入了尤里的圈套，因而华盛顿已经落入尤里的控制之中，并他已经在这里部署了一具心灵控制器，以巩固尤里在华盛顿的心灵控制。然而我们刚刚接到紧急求助，总统似乎并没来得及逃离华盛顿，仍然困在白宫之中。指挥官，不要动作慢吞吞的，让总统变成行尸走肉了。
 
任务目标一：在心灵信标再次部署之前将其摧毁
任务目标二：摧毁心灵控制器，解除超武威胁
任务目标三：清除所有尤里部队</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:All04md">在最近的多次战役中，我们始终出于被动的劣势，如今我们已经被逼上绝路。尤里这次逃脱确凿让他长了不少智慧，不过还好，我们还有爱因斯坦博士的王牌-时间机器，如果可以回到过去，我们仍然有机会赶在尤里实施一切阴谋之前就解决掉他。指挥官，这是我们最后的机会，时间机器务必不能被尤里摧毁！

任务目标一：死守时间机器直到其启动为止。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:ALL0Xmd">我们利用时间机器回到了过去，尤里已经派遣部队向希望角进发。如果我们可以防止尤里得到我们的超时空传送技术，或许这场战争将因此而改变。拿起武器战斗吧指挥官，新的历史将由您来改写。
 
任务目标一：与基地重新联络。
任务目标二：摧毁尤里的通讯基地。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:All05md">或许我们还是晚了一步，尤里早已获得一些超时空传送技术的研究成果。由于没有足够的技术支持，他们把目标定向了位于德国黑森林的爱因斯坦超时空科研基地，企图以心灵控制的方式来俘虏我们的科学家。据最新的军事情报，苏联这次也打算浑水摸鱼，趁机获利，这样一来我们将同时面对两个强大的对手。指挥官，无论如何必须守住这座实验室！
 
任务目标一：以最快速度摧毁尤里的心灵控制器，阻止其部署。
任务目标二：摧毁苏军基地以及苏军部队。
任务目标三：摧毁尤里的前线基地。
提示：我们必须保住超时空传送仪或爱因斯坦实验室其中一个</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:All06md">我们终于跟踪到了尤里超时空研究装置能量的发出地。它位于一座太平洋上一座未标明的小岛。我们已经准备好了一些部队，将以超时空传送的方式派去配合你的行动。指挥官，在这座陌生的岛屿，你一定要小心！
 
任务目标一：登陆岛屿，建立一座超时空机基地
任务目标二：摧毁或占领尤里的超时空实验装置
任务目标三：在尤里火箭发射之前，将其摧毁！</v>
  <v lbl="BRIEF:ALL07MD">我们在火箭的废墟中找到记录尤里飞行计划的黑匣子，它被设定飞往月球，我们认为尤里很有可能藏身于他的月球基地。为了弄清楚尤里真正的阴谋，我们派遣了一波特遣部队去调查，却与总部失去了联络。指挥官，征服月球，终结尤里这个恶魔！

任务目标一：守住火箭登陆台，等待援军到达。
任务目标二：占领尤里指挥中心，以获取尤里秘密档案
任务目标三：消灭所有尤里部队。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov01md">尤里居然没死！尽管我们并不知道尤里现在军事实力如何，但就克里姆林宫发来的紧急电报描述：莫斯科出现了一些尤里军队，并以最快的速度取得了一席之地，切断了总部与莫斯科军队的联络。将军，不管尤里是否还存在威胁，您首先必须清除莫斯科的垃圾，要快！

任务目标一：占领通讯中心与基地重新连线。
任务目标二：消灭所有尤里军队。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov02md">真是糟糕，由于我们忙于与应对尤里的突袭，一些组织严密的遗留的盟军已经开始反抗我们的政权统治，他们已将军队率领至海参威海域。将军，粉碎他们愚蠢而幼稚的计划吧！
 
任务目标一：建立一座基地。
任务目标二：消灭所有盟军。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov03md">将军，在我们疏忽间，盟军已经夺回了部分土地。据最新情报分析，美国总统现在回到了白宫之中。将军，您不希望世界上再蹦出一个与我们苏维埃相违背的资本主义政权吧？共产党的地位是不容动摇的，俘虏美国总统，使盟军重新归顺于我们！
 
任务目标一：建立一座军事后备基地。
任务目标二：消灭白宫周围的守卫部队，俘虏美国总统。
提示：摧毁标志性建筑可获得奖励</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov04md">尤里利用我们与盟军作战的时机，在摩洛哥建立了一座心灵控制器测试基地，如果成功的话意味着什么？我想大家都知道后果。将军，你一定要尽快摧毁心灵控制器，将他的阴谋扼杀在摇篮里！
 
任务目标一：消除心灵信标威胁，等待援军到达。
任务目标二：占领机场，获得盟军支援。
任务目标三：不惜一切代价摧毁心灵控制器。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov0xmd">尤里军队发展速度出乎我们的预料，总理和美国总统协商决定直捣其中心地区，逮捕尤里。此次行动十分冒险，将军大人，您必须时刻留意突发情况！

任务目标一：在尤里控制我方军队之前，摧毁心灵控制增幅仪
任务目标二：摧毁尤里要塞，逮捕尤里</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov05md">紧急情况！正当我们要宣布世界和平协议正式签署的时候，我们的卫星、空间站工作人员发现了一大群未知物体正在迅速逼近地球，并且其中一部分已经接近月球。据了解，这是来自T80星云—安塔列星人的部队。看来他们打算首先占领月球，再获得对地球的控制指挥，将地球变成他们的殖民地！好了将军，我们又有的打了！
 
任务目标一：保卫好实验中心，直到研究出新式武器。
任务目标二：锁定并摧毁外星人的月球通讯基地。
任务目标三：迅速返回地球。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov06md">将军，安塔列的袭击势如破竹，我们勉强消灭了抵达月球的安塔列前线部队，却给予了它们充分的时间抵达地球。莫斯科的前线已经失守，如果其沦陷，这将是巨大的灾难！虽然仅有的星际战舰已经被派往地球各个战略要冲，而好消息是，盟军和部分投降的尤里军队将加入我们共同对抗安塔列星人，你将被许可使用他们的科技。这是一场胜负未知的较量，打起精神，将安塔列的臭虫赶出莫斯科吧！
 
任务目标一：增援克里姆林宫，协助总理撤离。
任务目标二：配合心灵信标，抵挡安塔列的进攻。
任务目标三：消灭剩余的安塔列部队。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:Sov07md">我们追踪到罗马尼亚的尤里老巢有不明反应，经证实，此处驻守的盟军和苏军基地已与总部失去联络，并且正在从事一些有规律的科研活动。总理担心这是个阴谋。此次行动比较隐秘，因此您必须以最快的速度建设好基地，并将资料带离要塞。

任务目标一：摧毁心灵信标，解放当地的盟军和苏军
任务目标二：派遣特工潜入要塞，将资料带离</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN01">尤里总理现在被困太平洋监狱中。将军，虽然这里防御严密，但是我们我们已准备好军备，在东岸找到了一个登陆点，务必要把总理救出来，我们将东山再起！

任务目标一：进入心灵隔离室，救出尤里总理。
任务目标二：寻找并解救基地车。
任务目标三：修复并启动心灵信标，俘虏美军部队。
任务目标四：将总理安全带入直升机，并撤离</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN02">我们已经成功救出了总理，并且也重新组建了部分军队，但是由于我们的物资有限，必须获得一个军事根据地。我们把目标瞄准了尤里岛，而且组织了一支精英部队进行行动。但是请注意，苏军此时正不满盟军的独裁，也已经向该岛发起进攻，利用苏联与美军的矛盾，不要让尤里总理失望！

任务目标一：占领盟军作战实验室，控制火箭发射座
任务目标二：消灭剩余不投降的美军，占领岛屿</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN03">我们已经占领了尤里岛，并且重新修复了登月设备，准备登陆月球实施制空计划。将军，此处似乎有许多军队和一些重要的军事机密，你一定要窃取到他们的武器设计图！

任务目标一：摧毁苏军控制中心，使其失去控制
任务目标二：占领指挥中心，获得对苏军基地的控制权
任务目标三：在美军援军到达前摧毁信号传送塔</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN04">我们已经在月球上占据了一席之地，但是苏联红军对我们仍然构成了很大威胁。尤里总理打算在莫斯科部署一具心灵信标，控制住苏联的心脏地带，就等于控制了整个苏联红军。当然，莫斯科防卫十分严密，贸然行动只会让我们损失过多的军队。因此我们派出了一支特遣部队，给苏联一个措手不及，当他们反应过来的时候，已经在我们心灵信标的控制之下了。

任务目标一：占领苏联作战实验室，以建立一座心灵信标。
任务目标二：启动心灵信标，俘虏周围的苏军部队。
任务目标三：消灭莫斯科所有苏联防卫军，俘虏洛马诺夫。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN05">苏联总理投降了，下一个目标就是美国总统。目前看来，美国的军事力量是盟军中最强的，并且他们拥有威胁性极大的光棱科技。将军，我们必须以最快的速度控制住美国，才能实现最终的目的。

任务目标一：将意志宣传车送到苏联基地，获得对其的控制权。
任务目标二：占领盟军作战实验室，获得光棱科技。
任务目标三：占领白宫，俘虏美国总统。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN0X">时间所剩不多，由于苏军的能量过度释放，尤里总理已被困于侏罗纪。据最新情报，美军在苏联胜利之后又偷偷建立了一座时间机器，似乎想回到过去以挽回战局。我们集结了一些部队，希望可以占领那座时间机器，把尤里总理救回来。
 
任务目标一：摧毁摧毁海岸防御设施与美军舰队。
任务目标二：占领时间机器。
任务目标三：干掉暴龙，让尤里总理进入我们的时间机器。
提示：苏联人可不会坐视不管，随时提防他们的突然进攻。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN06">我们的心灵科技小组已经改进了心灵控制器的部分性能，打算在南极洲进行测试，并且顺便占领这里的一座盟军废弃的超时空传送仪以研究超时空移动科技。将军，小心行事，盟军随时可能发觉我们，动作一定要快！

任务目标一：占领超时空传送仪，等待援军到达。
任务目标二：摧毁天气控制机，并建立心灵控制器。
任务目标三：消灭剩余的所有苏、盟军队。
提示：超时空机器不能被毁</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN07">美国军团现在已经穷途末路了。他们拿出了最后的王牌——时间机器来做最后的赌注。我们岂能让美国佬再度嚣张？将军，痛击美国吧。相信这次战役将是美军的终场，完结这华丽的篇章吧。

任务目标一：派遣步兵占据通讯中心。
任务目标二：锁定并摧毁时间机器。
任务目标三：寻找并占领秘密实验室，获得心灵科技。
任务目标四：建立一座心灵信标，并等待其部署。</v>
  <v lbl="Brief:TRN08">盟军解散了！多么令人振奋的消息！但是等一下，盟军之前的将军卡维利和苏联的维拉迪摩将军集结了残存的部队，并且在珍珠港建立了海军基地。他们算是最后的首领了，将军，逮捕苏、盟的将军，并将他们就地正法！

任务目标一：清除岛屿驻扎军队，登陆并建立一座基地
任务目标二：登陆珍珠港，找到卡维利将军和维拉迪摩将军
任务目标三：将苏、盟将军带到苏联基地，等待其和苏联基地同归</v>
<!--LoadMsg section-->
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All01md">军事行动：紫色光影 - 地点：太平洋军事监狱</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All02md">军事行动：空间危机 - 地点：阿拉斯加希望角</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All03md">军事行动：自由与服从 - 地点：华盛顿</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All04md">军事行动：孤注一掷 - 地点：撒哈拉沙漠（最高机密地点）</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:ALL0XMD">军事行动：错乱时空 - 地点：阿拉斯加希望角</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All05md">军事行动：黑色黄昏 - 地点：德国，黑森林</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All06md">军事行动：空间裂缝 - 地点：太平洋中一个未标明的小岛</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:All07md">军事行动：蓝皮书计划 - 地点：月球</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:ALL08MD">军事行动：__ - 地点：__</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov01md">军事行动：风云再起 - 位置：莫斯科</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov02md">军事行动：躁动 - 地点：海参威</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov03md">军事行动：统治者行动 - 地点：美国，华盛顿特区</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov04md">军事行动：北非突袭 - 地点：摩洛哥</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:SOV0XMD">军事行动：终极对决 - 位置：罗马尼亚</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov06md">军事行动：四面楚歌 - 地点：莫斯科</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov05md">军事行动：深度拦截 - 地点：月球</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:Sov07md">军事行动：隐秘打击 - 地点：罗马尼亚</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:SOV08MD">军事行动：__ - 地点：__</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN01">军事行动：东山再起 - 地点：太平洋军事监狱</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN02">军事行动：深海突袭 - 地点：太平洋，复活节岛</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN03">军事行动：探月者 - 地点：月球</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN04">军事行动：莫斯科的黄昏 - 地点：莫斯科</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN05">军事行动：华盛顿暴动 地点：华盛顿</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN06">军事行动：极地心魔 地点：南极洲顶点</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN07">军事行动：逃逸或是服从 地点：加州，旧金山</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN08">军事行动：就地正法 - 地点：太平洋，珍珠港</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TRN0X">隐秘军事行动：时空之乱  地点：加州，旧金山</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:RES01">生化危机：黎明</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TEST01">任务调试：盟军</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TEST02">任务调试：苏军</v>
  <v lbl="LoadMsg:TEST03">任务调试：尤里</v>
<!--LoadBrief section-->
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All01md">任务目标一：派谭雅进入北方的基地，与基地重新取得联络。
任务目标二：摧毁心灵控制器。
任务目标三：谭雅不能殉职。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All02md">任务目标一：摧毁心灵信标，解救我方沿海基地。
任务目标二：占领作战室以备份并销毁所有我方资料。
任务目标三：在尤里再次启动超时空传送仪之前，将其摧毁。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All03md">任务目标一：在心灵信标再次部署之前将其摧毁
任务目标二：摧毁心灵控制器，解除超武威胁
任务目标三：清除所有尤里部队</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All04md">任务目标一：死守时间机器直到其启动为止。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All0xmd">任务目标一：与基地重新联络。
任务目标二：摧毁尤里的通讯基地。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All05md">任务目标一：以最快速度摧毁尤里的心灵控制器，阻止其部署。
任务目标二：摧毁苏军基地以及苏军部队。
任务目标三：摧毁尤里的前线基地。
提示：必须保住超时空传送仪或爱因斯坦实验室其中一个</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All06md">任务目标一：登陆岛屿，建立一座超时空机基地
任务目标二：摧毁或占领尤里的超时空实验装置
任务目标三：在尤里火箭发射之前，将其摧毁！</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:All07md">任务目标一：守住火箭登陆台，等待援军到达。
任务目标二：占领尤里指挥中心，以获取尤里秘密档案
任务目标三：消灭所有尤里部队。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov01md">任务目标一：占领通讯中心与基地重新连线。
任务目标二：消灭所有尤里军队。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov02md">任务目标一：建立一座基地。
任务目标二：消灭所有盟军。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov03md">任务目标一：建立一座军事后备基地。
任务目标二：消灭白宫周围的守卫部队，俘虏美国总统。
提示：摧毁标志性建筑可获得奖励</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov04md">任务目标一：消除心灵信标威胁，等待援军到达。
任务目标二：占领机场，获得盟军支援。
任务目标三：不惜一切代价摧毁心灵控制器。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov0xmd">任务目标一：在尤里控制我方军队之前，摧毁心灵控制增幅仪。
任务目标二：摧毁尤里要塞，逮捕尤里</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov05md">任务目标一：保卫好实验中心，直到研究出新式武器。
任务目标二：锁定并摧毁外星人的月球通讯基地。
任务目标三：迅速返回地球。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov06md">任务目标一：增援克里姆林宫，协助总理撤离。
任务目标二：配合心灵信标，抵挡安塔列的进攻。
任务目标三：消灭剩余的安塔列部队。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:Sov07md">任务目标一：摧毁心灵信标，解放当地的盟军和苏军
任务目标二：派遣特工潜入要塞，将资料带离</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN01">任务目标一：进入心灵隔离室，救出尤里总理。
任务目标二：寻找并解救基地车。
任务目标三：修复并启动心灵信标，俘虏美军部队。
任务目标四：将总理安全带入直升机，并撤离</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN02">任务目标一：占领盟军作战实验室，控制火箭发射座
任务目标二：消灭剩余不投降的美军，占领岛屿</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN03">任务目标一：摧毁苏军控制中心，使其基地失去控制
任务目标二：占领指挥中心，获得对苏军基地的控制权
任务目标三：在美军援军到达前摧毁信号传输塔</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN04">任务目标一：占领苏联作战实验室，以建立一座心灵信标。
任务目标二：启动心灵信标，俘虏周围的苏军部队。
任务目标三：消灭莫斯科所有苏联防卫军，俘虏洛马诺夫。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN05">任务目标一：将命令送到苏联基地，获得对其的控制权。
任务目标二：占领盟军作战实验室，获得光棱科技。
任务目标三：占领白宫，俘虏美国总统。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN06">任务目标一：占领超时空传送仪，等待援军到达。
任务目标二：摧毁天气控制机，并建立心灵控制器。
任务目标三：消灭剩余的所有苏、盟军队。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN07">任务目标一：派遣步兵占据通讯中心。
任务目标二：锁定并摧毁时间机器。
任务目标三：寻找并占领秘密实验室，获得心灵科技。
任务目标四：建立一座心灵信标，并等待其部署。</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN08">任务目标一：清除岛屿驻扎军队，登陆并建立一座基地
任务目标二：登陆珍珠港，找到卡维利将军和维拉迪摩将军
任务目标三：将苏、盟将军带到苏联基地，等待其和苏联基地同归</v>
  <v lbl="LoadBrief:TRN0X">任务目标一：摧毁摧毁海岸防御设施与美军舰队。
任务目标二：占领时间机器。
任务目标三：干掉暴龙，让尤里总理进入我们的时间机器。
提示：苏联人可不会坐视不管，随时提防他们的突然进攻。</v>
  <v lbl="Mission:ExtremeHam">Extreme Ham</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Objective1">Objective 1 Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Objective2">Objective 2 Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Objective3">Objective 3 Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01a">Objective 1: Assign your infantry to enter the Psychic Isolation Chamber to save Premier Yuri, ATTENTION: DO NOT DESTROY THE CHAMBER.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01b">ATTENTION: Premier Yuri came out, keep him safe.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01c">MCV received, ready to build the base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01d">Reinforcements have arrived, waiting for your orders.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01e">Objective 4: Send Premier Yuri to the helicopter and get out from here.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01f">Satellite has reconnected.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01g">HINT: Repair the bridge so that our forces can go and pass.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01h">There's no ore or gems here, capture the OIL DERRICK to acquire resources.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01i">Objective 3: Capture and activate the Psychic Beacon.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01j">MCV is sighted! Go for it right now!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01k">Repair the abandoned Psychic Beacon.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02b">Objective 1: Capture the Allied Battle Lab, and control the Rocket Launch Pad.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02c">General, here's an open space, you can land here and build the base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02d">Elite naval forces have arrived, awaiting orders.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02e">ALERT: Allied Battle Lab is destroyed, we lost control of the rocket.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02f">ALERT: Launch Pad structure lost. Mission Failed.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02g">Objective 2: Destroy all enemy Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02h">Objective 1 Completed.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02i">WARNING: Soviet naval forces detected.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02_Hint1">Deploy your GIs near the entrance to your base for a better defense</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02_Hint2">The Premier successfully retreated. Mission Accomplished.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02_Hint3">Now is not the time for potty breaks, Commander</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02_Hint4">No time to sit, Commander</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02hAlt">WARNING: The stench of Red Team is in the air</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01a">Objective 1: Destroy all four Soviet DREADNOUGHTS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01b">Objective 2: Rendezvous with FORT BRADLEY</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01c">HINT: Order your GI's to enter CIVILIAN BUILDINGS to fortify them</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01d">HINT: Fuel barrels explode if destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01e">HINT: Your base is out of power, build more power plants</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01f">HINT: Construct a BARRACKS in order to produce ENGINEERS to repair the bridge</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01g">HINT: GI's must DEPLOY to enter or exit their sandbagged foxholes</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01h">Objective 3: Destroy the Soviet SUPPLY BASE</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01i">WARNING: Soviet PARATROOPERS are incoming</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02a">Head NORTH and make contact with American forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02b">Objective 1: Use ENGINEERS to re-capture our base to the NORTH WEST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02c">Objective 2: Destroy all hostile forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02d">HINT: Order an ENGINEER into any HOSTILE BUILDING to capture the building</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02e">HINT: Order TANYA to destroy the FLAK CANNONS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02f">HINT: TANYA can swim</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04a">Objective 1: Clear enemy shore defenses with your Destroyers, then land and establish a base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04b">Objective 2: Destroy the Soviet's Psychic Amplifier before it comes online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04c">Estimated time until Psychic Amplifier is online:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All09a">Objective 1: Capture or Eliminate Soviet Research Facility within the Pyramid Ruins</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All09b">Objective 2: Destroy the Soviet base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All09c">Objective 1 Accomplished</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All09d">Objective 2 Accomplished</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov01a">Objective 1: Destroy the Pentagon</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1b">HINT: Order an ENGINEER into the BRIDGE HUT to repair the bridge</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1c">HINT: Order your CONSCRIPTS to enter CIVILIAN BUILDINGS to fortify them</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1d">HINT: FLAK TRACKS can carry TROOPS into battle</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1e">HINT: Your base is OUT OF POWER, build Power Plants</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1f">HINT: Fuel barrels EXPLODE if destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1g">HINT: Capture the AIRPORT with an ENGINEER to allow your paratroopers to land in the area</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02a">Objective 1: Force a beach landing and build a base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02b">Objective 2: Destroy all enemy forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02c">Vladimir: Now is the time to strike</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02d">Vladimir: What are you waiting for General? Do something!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02e">Enemy Fleet detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02f">Vladimir has fled the battlefield!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02g">Your Mobile Construction Vehicle has landed. Double-click on it to create a Construction Yard</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03a">Objective 1: Capture the Allied BATTLE LAB with an ENGINEER</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03b">Technology gained - Build a PSYCHIC BEACON</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03bb">Technology gained - PSYCHIC BEACON placed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03c">Objective 2: Defend the PSYCHIC BEACON from Allied attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03d">Beacon Deployment in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03e">Allied troops are now under Soviet control</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03f">Objective 3: Defeat all remaining Allied troops</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04a">Time until Allied invasion begins:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04b">Hint: Build Flak Cannons to engage Allied aircraft</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04c">Allied Forces have landed!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04d">Objective 1: Establish a base to defend our motherland</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov04e">Objective 2: Drive the Allied invaders back into the sea</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov05a">Objective 1: Energize the PARIS TOWER with 3 TESLA TROOPERS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov05b">Objective 2: Defend the PARIS TOWER from Allied attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov05c">Objective 3: Defeat all remaining Allied troops</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov05d">HINT: Cars + Bombs = CarBombs!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06b">Estimated time until Korean Fleet arrives:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07a">Objective 1: Defend your Battle Lab against waves of Allied attackers</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07b">General Carville has stationed a truck near one of our villages; He has been broadcasting capitalist propaganda in an attempt to turn our people against us</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07c">I think we should send a few dogs to sniff out enemy spies</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07d">The first wave of Allied troops have entered the Chronosphere</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07e">Another Allied force has entered the Chronosphere</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07f">The final Allied troops have entered the Chronosphere</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07g">You've captured a powerful new enemy vehicle! Try putting different infantry inside to enhance the vehicle's abilities</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07h">CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST: Our Battle Lab has been captured</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07i">CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST: Spies have infiltrated our Battle Lab</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07j">CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST: Our Battle Lab has been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov08a">Objective 1: Capture the White House so we can apprehend the traitor Vladimir</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov08b">Destroy monuments for cash bonuses from the Kremlin!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov09a">Objective 1: Use Mind-Control to capture the President</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov09b">Use America's own soldiers against them</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov09c">Enemy bases detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov09d">Order spies to enter power plants to sabotage base power</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov10a">Objective 1: Capture the BATTLE LAB with an ENGINEER</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov12a">Build naval forces and invade the Allied base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov12b">Move north and reclaim our captured Kirov airships</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov12c">Objective 1: Destroy the Allied CHRONOSPHERE</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12a">Objective 1: Clear the area so Chrono Reinforcements can arrive</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12b">Objective 2: Eliminate Romanov's Elite Black Guard around the Kremlin.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12c">Objective 2 Accomplished - Romanov has been captured</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12d">Objective 1 Accomplished - Chrono Reinforcements can now arrive</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12e">Alliance formed with Soviet Defectors</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12f">Soviet resource stockpile detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12g">Allied chrono reinforcements in transit, arriving soon</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN01cc">Move your troops across the bridge</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TRN02iAlt">Objective 2: Deploy your MCV into a Construction Yard</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01j">Secondary Objective Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01k">New Objective Received</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01l">HINT: Seals can SWIM and PLANT C4 like Tanya</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01m">HINT: Cars can be used to CARRY INFANTRY. To remove passengers, double-click on the car</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01n">HINT: Chrono Harvesters HARVEST ore and then automatically TELEPORT back to their refinery</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01o">HINT: Select the infantry TAB to view additional PRODUCTION OPTIONS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01p">HINT: Order your ENGINEER into one of the REPAIR HUTS in order to fix the bridge</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01q">--Battle Control Online--</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01r">Additional troops gained</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01s">HINT: To REMOVE your troops, DOUBLE-CLICK on the occupied building</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01t">HINT: DOUBLE-CLICK the GI's to switch them between DEPLOYED and MOBILE states</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01u">These GI's have deployed their heavy machine guns.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01v">Tanya has died - CRITICAL UNIT LOST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01w">The STATUE OF LIBERTY has been destroyed - CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01x">The STATUE OF LIBERTY is about to be destroyed - Hurry and destroy the Dreadnoughts!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL01y">HINT: To REMOVE your troops, SELECT the occupied building, then click on it again.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02g">Keep TANYA alive!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02h">TANYA has been KILLED!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL02i">so the ROCKETEERS can destroy the SENTRY GUNS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03a">Objective 1: Destroy the Psychic Beacon</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03b">You have salvaged Allied units abandoned after the Soviet invasion</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03c">HINT: Beware of SOVIET TROOPS garrisoned in CIVILIAN STRUCTURES</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03d">HINT: Be careful NOT to destroy the White House... we don't want to endanger the President</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03e">MISSION FAILED: Nice job commander. You've managed to crush the President under a huge slab of concrete...</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03f">HINT: Send an ENGINEER into a damaged CIVILIAN STRUCTURE to repair it</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03g">HINT: Try putting different INFANTRY in your new IFV to use its morphing ability</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03h">MISSION FAILED: President Dugan is but a flattened shell of a man</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03i">Straggler units from across the Potomac have gathered up near the Lincoln Memorial</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03j">A brave group of Allied survivors has scraped together a squad near the Smithsonian</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03k">HINT: Order an ENGINEER into an IFV to transform it into a Mobile Repair Vehicle</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04d">Reinforcements have just arrived from our Canadian base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04e">More reinforcements have just arrived from across Lake Michigan</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04f">HINT: Enemy SUB PATROLS are all over Lake Michigan. Land your transports quickly to avoid losses</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04g">Objective 2: Destroy the Psychic Amplifier before it comes online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04h">HINT: Send INFANTRY into the HOSPITAL to restore them to full health</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04i">HINT: These OIL DERRICKS, if captured, will yield a steady flow of cash</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04j">Clear the shore defenses with your Destroyers, then land and establish your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05a">Objective 1: Infiltrate the Soviet Battle Lab with a Spy</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05b">Objective 2: Eliminate the two Soviet Nuclear Missile Silos</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05c">HINT: SPIES can disguise themselves as ENEMY TROOPS</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05d">HINT: To disguise a SPY, select him and left click on an ENEMY SOLDIER</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05e">Tesla Coil detected - CAUTION: EXTREME DANGER</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05f">Additional Spies have arrived</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05g">Allied patrol discovered</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05h">Secondary Objective Complete - NEW OBJECTIVE RECEIVED</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05i">Primary Objective Complete - MISSION SUCCESSFUL</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05j">Bovine rescued</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05k">Tanya has died - CRITICAL UNIT LOST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05l">The Battle Lab has been destroyed - CRITICAL STRUCTURE LOST</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05m">First Nuclear Missile Silo destroyed - one remaining</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05n">First Nuclear Missile Silo has been captured - one remaining</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05o">HINT: Send a SPY into a TESLA REACTOR to shut down all base defenses</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05p">Silo coordinates acquired successfully - Enlarging map size to compensate</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05q">--Battle Control Online--</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05r">Somewhere in Poland...</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All05s">Signal Flare Detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07b">WARNING - SOVIET ATTACK IMMINENT</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08T">Time until Beacon affects Tanya:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10a1">HINT: When the MIRAGE TANK stops, it</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10a2">cloaks itself as a TREE and waits to ambush</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10a3">passing enemy forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10c">WARNING: Einstein's Laboratory is under attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10e">Objective 2: Destroy all Soviet invaders</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11d">Objective 1: Construct a Chronosphere</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12h">Tanya lost</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All12i">Kremlin Infiltrated - PRIMARY OBJECTIVE COMPLETE</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov02h">Build a NAVAL YARD so you can construct SUBMARINES</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov03aa">HINT: Capture the OIL DERRICKS for extra resources</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06c">A small fleet of the new Soviet Dreadnought has arrived</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06d">A small fleet of the new Soviet Dreadnought has arrived.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07k">Allied Spy Sat maps were found in the Propaganda Truck wreckage... updating map.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov08c">Destroy monuments for bonuses from the Kremlin!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov08d">Objective 1: Capture the White House</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11a">Objective 1: Destroy the KREMLIN, where YURI is cowering</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11b">WARNING: Enemy air armada detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11c">WARNING: Yuri has detected our Nuclear Missile Silo - Defend it well</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11d">HINT: To stop Kirov Airships, build lots of Flak Cannons</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11e">Hey! You're not supposed to be here!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11f">11/21/98</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11g">Power-up Crate discovered!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11h">NOX ROX!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11i">Warning, Iron Curtain device detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11j">Warning, the Iron Curtain device has rendered some of Yuri's troops invulnerable</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11k">TSC&amp;ACC</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11l">WARNING: Enemy Armor Brigade detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11m">WARNING: Enemy Infantry Platoon detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov11n">WARNING: Enemy Naval Fleet detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06a1">Objective 1: Reinforce and take command</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06a2">of Allied forces near the Pentagon</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06b1">Objective 2: Eliminate all Soviet forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06b2">occupying Washington, DC</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06c1">HINT: The SERVICE DEPOT can safely remove</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06c2">Soviet TERROR DRONES from infected vehicles</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06d1">Pentagon forces transferred to your command</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All06d2">Objective 1 Accomplished</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07a1">Objective 1: Destroy all Soviet forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07a2">on or around the Hawaiian Islands</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07c1">HINT: The GAP GENERATOR will conceal your</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All07c2">base from Soviet nuclear attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08a1">Objective 1: Capture or Destroy the</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08a2">Psychic Beacon before it affects your team</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08b1">Objective 2: Drive all Soviet forces out</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08b2">of St. Louis</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08c1">WARNING: Soviet Desolators have irradiated</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08c2">the ground at this location</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08d1">WARNING: The Psychic Beacon has affected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08d2">your team</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10b1">ALERT! Soviet Invasion Forces Detected. ALERT!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10d1">Objective 1: Defend Professor Einstein's</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All10d2">Laboratory</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11a1">HINT: To make SQUID release a ship, you</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11a2">must force your DOLPHINS to fire on the</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11a3">AFFECTED SHIP</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11b1">HINT: The CHRONOSPHERE will teleport all</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11b2">VEHICLES within a small area across any distance</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11c1">WARNING: Soviet Nuclear Missiles are now</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11c2">being armed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11e1">Objective 2: Neutralize the Soviet Nuclear</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11e2">Missile Silos</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All11T">Nuclear Strike in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06d1">Use them for long range shore bombardment.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov6a">Objective 1: Establish a base on the Hawaiian Islands</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov06g">Objective 2: Destroy the Allied fleet</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07L">Enemy Forces Arriving In:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1H">Iwo Jima Victory Monument, Washington D.C.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov10d">MISSION CRITICAL STRUCTURE - Do not destroy!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov10b">HINT: Build a NUCLEAR MISSILE SILO</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov10c">Objective 2: Destroy the Weather Control Device</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All08e">Bonus Discovered. Timer Extended.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL12y">Special Agent Tanya has arrived.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL12z">Final Objective: Tanya will infiltrate the Kremlin and Capture Romanov</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All03m">HINT: Order GIs into nearby CIVILIAN BUILDINGS to fortify them.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:HINTGENERAL">HINT: Order CONSCRIPTS into nearby CIVILIAN BUILDINGS to fortify them.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04k">HINT: AIR UNITS are very effective for assaults on Soviet-occupied civilian structures</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04l">Objective 1: Establish a base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL11zz">Order a SPY into an enemy NUKE to reset the count down.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ALL12zz">Romanov must be captured. Don't destroy the Kremlin!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All04m">Deploy your Mobile Construction Vehicle into a Construction Yard</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GetPower">Objective: Capture Power Plants to bring the Time Machine online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:KillRuss">Objective: Destroy all Soviet tanks</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Alcatraz">Objective: Swim Tanya to Alcatraz Island and destroy the Psychic Dominator</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Soviets">Objective: Clear the area of Soviet forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Carriers">Aircraft Carrier reinforcements have arrived</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Seals">SEAL reinforcements have arrived</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TimeText">Time Machine:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Swim">Hint: Tanya can swim to Alcatraz Island</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GrandC">Hint: Use the Grand Cannons to take out the Nuclear Reactor on Alcatraz</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GrandC2">Hint: Use the Grand Cannons to take out Soviet Dreadnoughts</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Tanya2">Hint: Tanya can plant C4 charges on tanks</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Soviet2">WARNING - Soviet armor battallion detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Attack">WARNING - The Time Machine is under attack!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Attack2">WARNING - Our Power Plants are under attack</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Attack3">WARNING - Do not attack Power Plants!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GattCann">WARNING - Gattling Cannon detected</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LoseTM">The Time Machine has been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LosePowr">There are not enough Power Plants left to charge the Time Machine</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Grinders">Objective: Destroy all Grinders in the city</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriBase">Objective: Destroy all enemy buildings</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LAX">Hint: Capture LAX to gain access to paratroopers</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Money">Hint: We may be able to salvage funds from Yuri's Grinders when they are destroyed.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Heroes">Hint: Action Heroes are excellent against infantry. Use them to eliminate Yuri Clones</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Lose">Your base has been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RescueMS">Secondary Objective: Liberate the MassiveSoft Campus from Yuri's goons</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:KillNuke">Objective: Destroy Yuri's Nuclear Silo</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RescueEinstein">Objective: Rescue Einstein from Yuri's secret base near the Great Pyramid</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyYuri04A">Objective: Destroy Yuri's main base in the East</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DerrickHint">Hint: Send engineers into the oil derricks in the East to increase cash flow</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:BoomerAttack">WARNING - Yuri is sending Boomer subs our way! Prepare for confrontation!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyCloning">Objective: Destroy Yuri's Cloning facility in the South</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyYuri05A">Objective: Destroy Yuri's remaining forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Fuego">Objective: Use engineers to bring the Soviet base back online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Radar">Objective: Build a Soviet Radar Dish</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:KillPD">Objective: Destroy the Psychic Dominator on Antarctica</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:KillYuri">Destroy all of Yuri's structures</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:FindRomanov">Objective: Locate Premier Romanov before Yuri's troops do</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RecoverRomanov">Objective: Rescue Romanov from Yuri's control</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyYuri04S">Objective: Destroy Yuri's base around the airport so Romanov can be safely evacuated</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TakeRomanov">Objective: Take Romanov to the airport where he can be transported away safely</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:BuildBase">Objective: Find a location to set up base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyLunarCommand">Objective: Locate and destroy Yuri's Lunar Command Center</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DestroyYuri06S">Objective: Destroy all remaining Yuri buildings</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:NukeHint">HINT: Yuri also relies on Power Plants for his Nuclear Silo</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sniper">Sniper reinforcements arriving</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:PowerAtk">WARNING - Our Power Plants are under attack!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Virus">Hint: Snipers have a longer range than the Virus</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Virus2">Hint: The Virus has a longer range than Snipers</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Cloud">WARNING - Infantry will take damage if standing within a Virus cloud</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LowPower">Capture Power Plants to bring the Weather Control Device online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Needle">Hint: Garrison the Space Needle to survey the area</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriMove">WARNING - Yuri is attempting to engineer our Power Plants</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriTimer">Yuri Forces Arriving In:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ParlHint">Hint: Repair Parliament with an Engineer</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:StopYuri">Objective: Destroy all Yuri forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MixUnits">Hint: Combine Soviet infantry with our IFV's for more powerful units</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:PDHint">Hint: Spread our units out so that the Psychic Dominator won't be able to mind control large masses of our forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GMHint">Hint: Spread out our infantry so that Yuri will not be able to use the Genetic Mutator on large groups of units.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TmeTimer">Time Machine Recharged in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TranHint">Hint: Build Amphibious Transports</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RexyHelp">Rexy is trapped! Won't you help him?</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RexyFrnd">Rexy is now your friend to the end!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:WarnStct">WARNING - Critical structure. Do not destroy!!!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MoreTrps">More of our troops have arrived on the beach</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MoreEngn">Engineers have arrived near the Time Machine</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriPowr">Yuri is trying to capture the Power Plants!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YGotPowr">Yuri captured a Power Plant!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:HintPowr">Hint: Capture Power Plants with Engineers</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DomArmed">The Psychic Dominator is now armed!!!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:HintDom">Hint: Capturing Power Plants will stop the Psychic Dominator</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:YuriHovr">Yuri Hover Transports approaching!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LostAll">All Soviet forces lost</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:NoTroops">No remaining Soviet forces</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LostStct">Critical Structure Lost</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:LostUnit">Critical Unit Lost</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:WarnArmd">WARNING - The Psychic Dominator is Armed!!!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:WrnAmbsh">WARNING - Possible Ambush Ahead!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:WarnSnpe">WARNING - Sniper detected!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:SecrtLab">Secret Laboratory Acquired!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ScrtTech">Secret Technology Acquired!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All6Obj1">Objective 1: Defend Parliament from Assault.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:All6Obj2">Objective 2: Destroy Yuri's Base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj1">Objective 1: Destroy the Allied Navy and Grand Cannons.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj2">Objective 2: Destroy Pill Boxes around Time Machine to capture it.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj3">Objective 3: Capture 4 Power Plants to Power Time Machine.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj4">Objective 4: Take Control of Soviet Base and use it to Destroy the Psychic Dominator.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj5">Objective: Defend the Time Machine until it can be reactivated.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj6">Find the Soviet Base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj7">Destroy the Psychic Dominator.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj1Comp">Objective 1 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj2Comp">Objective 2 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj3Comp">Objective 3 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj4Comp">Objective 4 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj5Comp">Objective 5 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj6Comp">Objective 6 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj7Comp">Objective 7 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj8Comp">Objective 8 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Obj9Comp">Objective 9 Complete.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov2Obj1">Objective 1: Destroy the outposts guarding the German border.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov2Obj2">Objective 2: Destroy Einstein's Lab and Chronosphere.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Mirage">WARNING - Mirage Tanks spotted!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MirageHint">Hint: Mirage tanks become visible if they move or fire.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:BattleFortress">WARNING - The Battle Fortress can crush tanks. Destroy them before they can close in.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:IndustrialHint">Hint: Build an Industrial Plant to speed up production.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:SpyPlaneHint">Hint: Use the Spy Plane to uncover shroud.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov3Obj1">Objective 1: Destroy the Psychic Beacon.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov3Obj2">Objective 2: Destroy the Psychic Dominator.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov3Obj3">Objective 3: Finish off Yuri's forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov5Obj1">Objective 1: Pick a landing zone and construct a base.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov5Obj2">Objective 2: Locate and destroy Yuri's Submarine Pen.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov5Obj3">Objective 3: Finish off all remaining Yuri land forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:MojoTip">Mojo 1</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Clones">HINT: Use attack dogs to deal with Yuri Clones and Initiates</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:AllGone">Our forces have been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GrabPowr">HINT: Capture Power Plants to bring the Weather Control Device back online</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ReinforcementsAll04md">Reinforcements have arrived and await orders from your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:RobotTanks">Hint: Robot Tanks are psychic immune</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:SniperDiscovered">Look, there was a sniper lost in the desert! He's happy to be a part of your team!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ImportDino">Thanks to ChronoSphere technology we were able import dinosaurs to help us defeat Yuri!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Mojo1All04md">You can feel the presence of Mojo One</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ReinforcementsAll05md">Reinforcements have arrived and await orders from your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:TopSecret">You've discovered something no one has ever seen before!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:BuildUp">Build up your defenses quickly before Yuri's attack forces arrive!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Boomers">WARNING - Boomer Subs spotted off the Antarctic coast</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Lose1">We have lost our foothold in Antarctica</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Lose2">All of our forces have been destroyed</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Lose3">We have lost the ability to build radar</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ReinforcementsSov04md">Reinforcements have arrived and await orders from your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:PolarBears">It looks like these bears were tired of the cold!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ReinforcementsSov06md">Reinforcements have arrived and await orders from your base</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:AllyBeacon">Hint: Capture or Destroy the Psychic Beacon in the Allied Base to release them from Yuri's control.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:SovBeacon">Hint: Neutralize the Psychic Beacon controlling the Soviet Base and they will rally to your side against Yuri.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov07Obj01">Objective: Destroy Yuri's Fortress.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:HiKBOAEO">KBO AEO</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ComboWarn01">WARNING - Yuri has begun mixing the technologies at his disposal.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ComboWarn02">Make ready for these attacks.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:GeneWarn">WARNING - Yuri's Genetic Mutator mutates normal soldiers, turning them into Brutes under Yuri's control.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C11Obj">Objective: Destroy all Soviet forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C11Nuke">Destroy the Soviets Nuclear Reactor.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C12Obj">Objective: Destroy all Yuri forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C12Spy">Hint: Use a Spy to shut down Yuri's power.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C13Def">Construct base defenses before enemy forces arrive.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C13Timer">Enemy forces arrive in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C13Warn">WARNING - Enemy troop movements detected.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C13Obj">Objective: Destroy all Yuri and Soviet forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C21Timer">Reinforcements arrive in:</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C21Grand">Destroy the Allied Grand Cannons.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C21Obj">Destroy all Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C22Gatt">Destroy Yuri's Gattling Cannon defenses.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C23Obj">Objective: Destroy all Yuri and Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C23Lab">Locate and capture Einstein's laboratory.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C23Nuke">Protect the Nuclear Reactors.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C31Obj">Objective: Destroy all Allied forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C31Crate">Hint: Destroy American monuments for a cash reward.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C32Navy">Build Boomer Submarines to destroy the Soviet Navy.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C33Obj">Objective: Destroy all Allied and Soviet forces.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C33">Hint: Target civilians with the Genetic Mutator to turn them into Brutes.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Combo">HINT:Try using combinations of Allied and Soviet units.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Hsptl">HINT: Capture the Tech Hospital to regenerate infantry health.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Mshop">HINT: Capture the Tech Machine Shop to regenerate vehicle armor.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Rig">HINT: Capture Tech Oil Derricks to increase cash flow.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:C41Air">HINT: Capture the Tech Airport for Airborne reinforcements.</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:ObjCompleteSov04md">Objective Complete</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:DominatorSelfDestruct">Psychic Dominator Self Destruct</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:PsychicTowers">WARNING - Psychic Towers can mind control enemy units that get too close to them!</v>
  <v lbl="MISSION:Sov1Obj2a">Destroy the Pill Boxes surrounding the Time Machine.</v>
